So, hi everyone.
I am Vanyel A. Carrera and I am a video specialist who
have two years of experience. So,
about my background, I started editing way back,
way back on 2011. Uhm, 2025. So,
initially, my main editing format and approach is for clipping.
Like, I do participate in different types of campaign,
like podcast clipping, sports,
content, creators clipping. So,
this one already. The example.
So, yeah, that's when I discovered AI Entertainment Video.
So, I decided to start making it for fun.
So, yeah, these ones are my sample works.
So, I did Skeletal and Skeleton animation before.
Then, that's when I discovered AI UGC and got interested in it.
Then, I started doing freelancing and used my portfolio to receive outsourced
projects. And then, I mastered the workflow of making it making AI
ads, and that's when I decided to start working under an agency and companies
which is the CBD Media and the AdMotion Studio,
which is both a DTC company. So, in there,
I handled different brands from different clients,
like, the UGC, this one. So,
it has different types of brands,
like, ah, supplements, ah,
gym equipment, ah,
Dutch product, ah, in Dutch language,
and then, ah, supplements and skin care.
Then, throughout my experience,
I created a lot of ads already. There are different types of ads that
I make. There are UGC,
this one, UGC animated,
and then VSL. So,
ah, ah, I'll show you an example of it, and why do I think
it's my best work for each category. So,
first one is this. Ah,
wait. Yeah.
First one is this, UGC animated.
It's actually hard to choose, because I think all of my works are my
best work, because I'm always putting my 100% in every project.
But here, here you go. This is a UGC for skincare.
Yeah, why do I think, why do I think it's a good AI video?
First, uh, it has a great hook.
Why? I'll tell you what it takes to make a great hook.
For me, hooks have three types. Visual hook,
audio hook, and text hook. to make a video.
I should meet all of these three,
or at least have one. Uh,
I think I did one on this video,
which is a visual hook. Because the very first frame of the video should
be the most engaging part. So as you can see,
I displayed a woman. We have an acne problem,
because that's, that's what the problem solves.
That's what the product solves.
So, yeah, since they already saw the problem
in the video, they will definitely, definitely solve it.
Stop scrolling, and look for the product system
of the video. And then the next hook is the text hook.
So, I think it's the best example of the text hook.
So, the main purpose of a text hook is
to give curiosity for the viewers.
So, suppose this one,
I mean, why would a pulmonologist,
uh, why would a pulmonologist is told a patient to
smoke? It's kind of ironic, right? So,
yeah, it gives curiosity. Then, that is a check.
So, you achieve the first hook, the text hook.
And then, the last hook is the actually by the way it's a four-minute
read. So, my VSL is usually have 30 to 40,
uh, three minutes to six minutes read.
So, yeah. Then, let's proceed with,
yeah, which is the audio hook. So,
uh, oh, I forgot to tell,
uh, you should also, should also have a good font for,
uh, a text hook cause,
uhm, yeah, but I don't think it's,
in this video, I don't think it's the best. Because the target audience is
40 plus old people, but the colors seem to ever,
too overwhelming for their eyes.
But I don't have a choice, it's the client preference,
so, I don't think I have much time left.
So, I will just create a part 2.
2 of the video, I hope it's totally fine,
and, yeah, see you guys.